Welcome to The Unit, Unusual Schools Around the World. A.
Kitty is listening to a programme about some unusual schools.
Listen with her and match the picture of each school with its country and the reason for creating it.
Now we are going to learn about some unusual schools around the world.
First, let's go to India.
Many poor families there do not have enough money to send their children to school.
Lots of children have to work at train stations or on trains to help support their families, so some teachers started schools for these children at the station.
Now, let's turn to Bangladesh.
Bangladesh often has floods when heavy rains hit the country, but children don't have to miss school.
A school boat picks the children up.
They have lessons on the boat, and then the boat takes them home.
Finally, the School of the Air in Australia.
Some people live on farms, hundreds of kilometres from the nearest school.
But children in these areas are able to use the internet to talk with their teachers and classmates.